Minji Kim

124 Charlton Blvd, Toronto ON, M2R 2J1 | (416) 821-3591

dalimanju15@gmail.com • www.linkedin.com/in/mkim9713 • https://github.com/MinJiKim123

PROFILE

Wide range of skill sets in object-oriented software development. An experienced back-end programmer with dynamic work experiences in software development specializing in C# and .NET. with strong knowledge of SDLC. Effective in both team and individual work environments, communicative, quick learner, and a talented problem solver.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Technology Advanced Diploma (Honours)

Sept. 2017 – Dec. 2020

Centennial College, Toronto, ON

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern

May 2020 - Aug 2020

Zenith I&T Robotic Process Automation (RPA), Seoul, Korea

- Successfully implemented RPA processes for the application of auto-execution on a remote production server using tools such as: Microsoft Automation API, PsTools, and SQL.
- Facilitated daily data export jobs by creating a web automation tool using Selenium, C#, and XML.

Software Developer Co-op

Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

RBC Enterprise & International Applications (E&IA), Toronto, ON

- Utilized Blue Prism RPA processes, .NET, Selenium, and SQL to develop an automation tool for *ServiceNow* incident ticketing process of 5+ different client applications.
- Assisted in creating an efficient C# tool to manage data from Active Directory using Directory Services library by extracting and exporting the data to excel.

Application Developer Co-op

Jan 2019 - Apr 2019

CIBC Personal Banking Products Technology (PBPT), Toronto, ON

- Supported in developing a user-friendly WPF tool to run calculation jobs and managed database-level user roles and privileges on different servers.
- Automated the daily execution of 10+ batch files to manage mortgage processes and to generate reports.

EXTRACURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

Peer Tutor

Centennial College Learning Centre, Toronto, ON

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

• Tutored 20+ students on technical skills: Java EE, C# (WPF), and Web development (MERN stack)

PROJECTS

EduCloud – MERN (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js) Stack, REST API, WebSocket, Google Dialogflow https://github.com/MinJiKim123/mk-mern-project

• Created a website in which students can communicate through chat function and schedule events via calendar

Movie4Share - ASP.NET, MVC Pattern, AWS S3, AWS DynamoDB, AWS Elastic Beanstalk

https://github.com/MinJiKim123/mk-aspnet-aws-uploadvideo

• Developed and published an interactive website that lets users to upload and download videos with reviews

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Web application development –Node.js, React.js, ASP.NET, HTML, CSS
- WPF development C#, .NET
- Data Management SQL, PL/SQL, NoSQL
- Java
- RPA (Robotic Process Automation) Selenium, BluePrism